{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"885","name":"Mark Twain K-8","address":"12800 Visger St","zipcode":"48217","owner":"BOARD OF ED CITY OF DETROIT","licenseNumber":"034919","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"210","coords":"-83.16215,42.26949","geojson":{"id":"885","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.162146005,42.269489064]},"properties":{"name":"Mark Twain K-8","owner":"BOARD OF ED CITY OF DETROIT","address":"12800 Visger St","zipcode":"48217","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"034919","establishmentid":"885","establishment_type":"Public School","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"210","most_recent_license_date":"6/1/2020"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622561","name":"The Paris Cafe","address":"2709 South Fort Street","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"4068","name":"Ella Mae's Place","address":"2251 S Fort Street","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"617","name":"New Paradigm College Prep School","address":"2450  S Beatrice St ","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"2245","name":"Perfect Beat","address":"1941 Fort St S","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"51622934","name":"Tacos Regios Mexican grill #2","address":"1781 S Fort St","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"51622742","name":"Lorent Coney Island","address":"601 S Schaefer Rd","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"2312","name":"Taqueria La Salsa Mexican Cuisine","address":"1310 Oakwood Blvd S","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"51622762","name":"D's Coney Island","address":"2626 S Schaefer Hwy","zipcode":"48217"},{"establishmentid":"5062","name":"Bag Of Bonez","address":"1250 S Beatrice St","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"4979","name":"Pathway Academy","address":"11340-43 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48214"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"49436","inspectionDate":"2019-10-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Handwashing sinks are to be accessible for use at all times"},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"rodents","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"and the KITCHEN","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"6-304.11","violationDescription":"If necessary to keep rooms free of excessive heat, steam, condensation, vapors, obnoxious odors, smoke, and fumes, mechanical ventilation of sufficient capacity shall be provided.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Mechanical ventilation hood","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Inadequate","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"VENTILATION","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate ventilation."},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room door(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Propped open","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Restroom(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Do not prop door open."}]},{"inspectionid":"47988","inspectionDate":"2019-06-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not accessible","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Handwashing sinks are to be accessible for use at all times"},{"violationCode":"6-304.11","violationDescription":"If necessary to keep rooms free of excessive heat, steam, condensation, vapors, obnoxious odors, smoke, and fumes, mechanical ventilation of sufficient capacity shall be provided.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Mechanical ventilation hood","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Inadequate","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"VENTILATION","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate ventilation."},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not tight-fitting","subProblem":"","location":"BACK DOOR AREA","subLocation":"At the Back door","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"rodents","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"and the KITCHEN","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"walls","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Debris","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room door(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Propped open","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Restroom(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Do not prop door open."},{"violationCode":"6-201.16","violationDescription":"(A) Wall and ceiling covering materials shall be attached so that they are EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n(B) Except in areas used only for dry storage, concrete, porous blocks, or bricks used for indoor wall construction shall be finished and SEALED to provide a SMOOTH, nonabsorbent, EASILY CLEANABLE surface.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wall/ceiling covering(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not attached","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Ceiling tile(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Securely attach to wall/ceiling."}]},{"inspectionid":"44267","inspectionDate":"2018-11-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Baseboard (tiles)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"rodents","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"and the KITCHEN","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not tight-fitting","subProblem":"","location":"BACK DOOR AREA","subLocation":"At the Back door","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements above."}]},{"inspectionid":"42415","inspectionDate":"2018-05-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"885"}}